eppraisal.com 2006-11-20

# Privacy Policy | eppraisal.com

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Saris Technologies, Inc. (“Saris”) respects each individual's right to privacy. This privacy policy discloses the information collection, use, and disclosure practices for our website (the "Site"). By accessing the Site, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of information as described herein. 

**Information We Collect**

_Personal Information_ When you register for a full eppraisal via our Site, you are required to provide non-public personal information (hereinafter “personal information”). You may not later be able to access, modify, or remove the information; however, you may choose simply not to provide the information. 

We collect personal information such as your email address, name, home address, telephone number. We also collect information about the property for which you are requesting information. We may collect demographic information such as your ZIP code, age, gender and preferences. Information we collect may be combined with information we obtained through other services we offer and from third parties. We may also collect information that your browser sends to web sites you visit like your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring web site addresses. 

Our Site may provide you with various services related to home selling, home buying, and financing, including estimates of current market value of homes, mortgage or finance costs, current home listings, neighborhood information, etc. 

_Aggregated Statistical Information_ Aggregated statistical information is data we collect about a group or category of products, services or users, from which individual user identities have been removed. We collect aggregate information about you and your use of our services and combine it with information about how others use the same services. Such aggregate information includes, without limitation, site traffic, page views, and impressions. This information may be correlated to you for our internal use only. However, we may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, sell, or otherwise disclose or use any and all aggregate information we collect. 

**Use and Disclosure of Information Collected**

Except as set forth in this privacy policy, we do not disclose, sell, rent, loan, trade or lease any personally identifying information collected at our Site to any non-affiliated third party. We will disclose personal information in the following circumstances: 

_Personal Information_ We use personal information in providing services to users, in processing users’ requests, informing users about products and services that may be of interest to them, informing users about third party service providers, telemarketing goods and services to users, anticipating and resolving problems with our Site, and in responding to customer support inquiries. We will use your personal information and share it with other third party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to you via direct mail, email and telemarketing. The businesses may include providers of direct marketing services including lookup and reference data enhancements, suppression and validation and email marketing. By providing this information to us, you expressly consent to being contacted by us and by third party professionals and service providers, via phone, fax, email, mail or other reasonable means, at any of your contact numbers or addresses, in order that we may provide the services set forth on our Site and for other reasonable purposes related to our services. 

_Internal Use_ We will use and disclose information about you for our own internal statistical, design or operational purposes. We may outsource these tasks and disclose personal information about you to third parties, provided the use and disclosure of your personal information by these third parties is restricted to performance of such tasks. We may also share personal information with third-party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. We require our third party vendors to keep such information confidential and to only use the information for the purpose it was provided. 

_Service Transactions_ We will disclose personal information to one or more third parties, as necessary, to provide you with the services. As stated above, your personal information is forwarded to one or more third party service providers (such as real estate agents, brokers, lenders and other real estate professionals) in order to provide you with the services. If a particular service provider is unable to fulfill your request within a reasonable time, we may forward your information to an alternate service provider to ensure that your request is fulfilled. Service providers may contact you to complete the transactions you have requested by any methods available including via e-mail, telephone, regular mail, in person visits or other means. We do not control how third party service providers use or disclose your personal information and are not responsible for removing your information from any third party lists. Please contact the third party service providers directly to be removed from their lists. 

_Protection of Saris and Others_ We disclose personal information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal process. 

_Business Transfers_ Information about users of our Site, including personally identifiable information provided to us by our users, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, financing or refinancing of debt, sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of the business assets of the company. 

_Links_ We may provide links to third party websites from our Site as a service to our users. We do not control and are not responsible for the content or data collection practices of those sites and the privacy policies of such sites may differ from that of Saris We recommend you review and understand the privacy policies of such sites before providing them with any information. 

_Information Protection_ We use reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our Site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. 

_Cookies_ Cookies are small files stored by your browser when you visit our Site. We use cookies to improve our Site and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests. We may use “session cookies” that are automatically deleted after each visit. Cookies from our Site can’t be read by other sites. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change browser settings to refuse them. 

_Third Party Ad Networks_ We may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on the Site. Some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks. 

_Children_ We do not intend, and this Site is not designed, to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old, you should not register for our services or otherwise provide information on our Site. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If we make any material changes, we will post a new statement on the Site and update the Effective Date set forth above. Please check the date of our privacy policy whenever you visit the Site. 

**Questions**

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy statement or the privacy practices of Saris or eppraisal, please email us at info@eppraisal.com or write to us at eppraisal, Privacy Officer, 255 S. Orange Avenue, Suite 600, Orlando, FL 32801. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California residents may request that Saris not share their personal information with third parties for their direct marketing use. To make such a request, please email us at info@eppraisal.com or write to us at : eppraisal, Privacy Officer, 255 S. Orange Ave., Ste. 600, Orlando, FL 32801. 

Saris Technologies, Inc.  
255 S. Orange Avenue, Ste. 600  
Orlando, FL 32801
